### Ayna Amrahova

### Software Engineer

Java Developer with 1 year of experience and a wide range of completed projects. Capable of designing the software for different clients, as well as providing technical support in evaluating the efficiency of finished and ongoing projects.

≥ ayna.amrah@gmail.com

Baku, Azerbaijan

github.com/Ayna-Amrahova

\_\_\_\_+994508977842

in linkedin.com/in/ayna-amrahova

### **EDUCATION**

# Information and CommunicationTechnology Azerbaijan Technical University

09/2016 - 07/2020

GPA 3.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Junior Software Developer Bank Respublika OJSC

04/2021 - Present

Baku, Azerbaijan

Work Details

- Wrote clean, clear and well-tested code for various projects.
- Designed and built scalable APIs to increase workflow.
- Improved code quality by through automated testing using.

## Trainee Junior Engineer Azercell Telecom LLC

07/2019 - 03/2021

Baku, Azerbaijan

Work Details

- Planned and installed systems based on customer needs.
- Read technical manuals and literature to stay abreast of new technology.
- Initiated improvements to operational efficiency of network.

### **SKILLS**



### **CERTIFICATES**

Java - Hackerrank

Lightbend, Inc. - Reactive Architecture: Building Scalable Systems

Lightbend, Inc. - Reactive Architecture: CQRS and Event Sourcing

Lightbend, Inc. - Reactive Architecture: Distributed Messaging Patterns

Lightbend, Inc. - Reactive Architecture: Domain Driven Design

Lightbend, Inc. - Reactive Architecture: Introduction to Reactive Systems

Lightbend, Inc. - Reactive Architecture: Reactive Microservices

### **LANGUAGES**

Azerbaijani

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

Turkish

Full Professional Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Technology

Programming

Researching